<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<item>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Guidliness</title>
    <desc>On the Internet usually the resume are send via e-mail to respective companies, but it is still important that you carry a copy along with you during your preliminary interview.</desc>
</item>
<item>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>Why do you Need a Resume?</title>
    <desc>A summary of your objectives,educational qualification,experience,skills relevant to the field of work you are going to enter.</desc>
</item>
<item>
    <id>3</id>
    <title>Basics of Writing a Resume</title>
                <subcategory>
                        <title>Basic Standards</title>
                        <desc>Resume is what an employer looks at much before meeting you,it is the first interface you have with your employer.</desc>
               </subcategory>
               <subcategory>
                       <title>Stick of the Point</title>
                       <desc>Employers have a busy schedule, so don't expect them to read through a long resume.</desc>
               </subcategory>
               <subcategory>
                   <title>Words Count</title>
                   <desc>Use of language is extremely important; you need to sell yourself to an employer quickly and efficiently.</desc>
               </subcategory>
               <subcategory>
                   <title>Make the Most of your Experience</title>
                   <desc>Employers need to know what you have accomplished to have an idea of what you can do for them. Don't be vague.</desc>
               </subcategory>
               <subcategory>
                   <title>Honesty is a Good Policy</title>
                   <desc>Employers will feel more comfortable hiring you if they can verify your accomplishments.</desc>
               </subcategory>
               <subcategory>
                   <title>Double-Check for Mistakes</title>
                   <desc>Check your resume for correct grammar and spelling - evidence of good communication skills and attention to detail.</desc>
               </subcategory>
</item>
<item>
    <id>4</id>
    <title>15 Golden Steps</title>
    <desc>The thought of writing a resume scares almost anyone. It's difficult to know where to start or what to include.</desc>
</item>
<item>
    <id>5</id>
    <title>8 Red Flags</title>
    <desc>A Resume is your mirror reflection to a recruiter or prospective employer.</desc>
</item>

</rss>
